Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/anthony-lawrence-amier-2b0587295 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Virtual Assistance Individual Work Adobe Photoshop

Anthony Lawrence Amier

Aspiring Virtual Assistant | Technical Support and Customer Service Experience

Naga, Bicol Region, Philippines

Summary

I am happy to provide various customer focused, technical, and creative services to clients across different industries. I have a good communication, organization, and problem-solving skills. I am also willing to learn new skills and adapt to different work environments and expectations.

Just to provide a brief history of my work background, I worked as a customer service and technical support agent in two of the finest call center companies in the Philippines, Quantrics Enterprises Inc. and Sutherland Global Services, for almost six years.

I handled multiple customer accounts (AMAZON) and resolved issues with professionalism and efficiency. I also leveraged my associate's degree in Computer Science in Networking Technology to troubleshoot technical problems (BELL CANADA) and provide solutions.

I am looking to leverage my experiences and skills to land my next job and support your business goals.

Experience

Self-employed Self Employed February 2023 - Present (1 year 11 months) Naga, Bicol Region, Philippines

Quantrics Enterprises Inc.
Technical Support Specialist
March 2022 - February 2023 (1 year)
Naga, Bicol Region, Philippines

Tech Support at Bell Canada

Sutherland
Customer Service Representative
September 2017 - November 2021 (4 years 3 months)
Pili, Bicol Region, Philippines

Agent at Amazon Retail Phones and Chat

Education

ACLC College

Associate's degree, Computer Systems Networking and Telecommunications · (June 2015 - March 2017)

University of Saint Anthony
High School Diploma · (June 2009 - March 2013)